Capital District Reference; Collection mss157
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Cohoes, 1953-1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Cohoes, All-American City Celebration, 1967 (Oversized 3, Folder 24)
- Cohoes, All-American City Celebration, Undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Cohoes, Business and Industry, 1955-1978 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Cohoes, Centennial, 1970; Undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Cohoes, Centennial, 1970 (Oversized 3, Folder 25)
- Cohoes, Community Development and Urban Renewal, 1967; 1969-1973; 1976-1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Cohoes Falls, 1912-1978 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Cohoes, Government and Politics, 1972; 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Cohoes Mastodon, 1974; 1977; Undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Cohoes Music Hall, 1975; 1977-1980; Undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Cohoes, Schools, Public, 1967 (Oversized 3, Folder 26)
- Cohoes, Schools, Public, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Colonie, 1963-1983; Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Corinth, 1965; 1977; Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Council of Upstate Ports New York, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Coxsackie, 1958; 1964; Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Defreestville, 1961; 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Delmar, 1953-1972; Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Delmar, Five Rivers Environmental Education Center, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- East Greenbush, 1950; 1955 (Oversized 3, Folder 27)
- East and North Greenbush, 1950-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Esperance, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Feura Bush and Bethlehem, 1950 (Oversized 3, Folder 28)
- Fort Edward, Rogers Island, 1962 (Oversized 3, Folder 29)
- Galway, 1973 (Oversized 3, Folder 30)
- Glenmont, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Glenmont, New York Job Corps Center, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Glens Falls, Adirondack Red Wings, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Granville, 1960; 1962 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Green Island, 1956; 1963 (Oversized 3, Folder 31)
- Green Island, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Green Island, Industry, 1962-1963; 1966; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Guilderland, 1956-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Hampton Manor, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Helderberg Mountains, 1939-1977 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Helderberg Mountains, 1951; 1954; 1959-1960 (Oversized 3, Folder 32)
- Helderberg Sun, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Herkimer, Nicholas, General, Postcards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Hoosick Falls, 1958; 1965-1966; 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Hudson, 1954-1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Hudson Falls, 1958-1961; 1963-1964; 1966 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Hudson, Olana, 1964-1966; 1971; 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Hudson River, Bannerman's Island, 1940; 1956; 1967; 1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Hudson River, Bridges, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Hudson River, Clearwater, 1966; 1969-1972; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Hudson River, Conservation and Preservation, 1948-1981; Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Hudson River, Description, 1963; 1965; 1979 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Hudson River, History, 1947-1984; Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Hudson River, Maps, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Hudson River, Navigation, 1959; 1962-1963; 1973; 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Hudson River, Pollution, 1966; 1969-1973; 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Hudson River, Recreation, 1966; 1979 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Hudson River Regulating District, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Hudson River, Steamboats, 1931-1980; Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Hudson River, Steamboats, 1938; 1948 (Oversized 3, Folder 33)
- Hudson Valley, Buildings and Places, Historic, ca. 1876; 1893-1903; 1910-1978 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Hudson Valley, Buildings, Historic, 1948; 1951 (Oversized 3, Folder 34)
- Hudson Valley, History, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Hudson Valley, Recreation, 1971; 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Johnstown, 1957-1960; 1968; 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Jordanville, Holy Trinity Monastery and Seminary, 1959; 1964; 1966; 1978; Undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Kinderhook, 1938; 1956; 1958-1959 (Oversized 3, Folder 35)
- Kinderhook, 1962; 1966; 1970; 1977; 1979 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Kinderhook, Martin Van Buren, 1954-1978 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Kinderhook, Martin Van Buren, 1965 (Oversized 3, Folder 36)
- Knickerbocker News, Five River Rambles, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Knickerbocker Press, New York State Education Building, 1922 (Oversized 3, Folder 37)
- Knickerbocker News, Who Runs Albany, 1968; Undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Lake George, Ice-A-Rama, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Lake Placid, John Brown Farm, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Latham, 1963; 1975 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Little Falls, Indian Castle Church, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Loudonville, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Loudonville, Sienna College, 1973; 1976-1980; Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
- McKnownville, 1959; 1963; 1980 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Mechanicville, 1954-1974; Undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Menands, 1960; 1962-1963; 1965; Undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Menands, Mohawk Hudson Humane Society, 1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Middleburgh, 1949 (Oversized 3, Folder 38)
- Middleburgh, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Nassau, 1949 (Oversized 4, Folder 1)
- Nassau, 1966; 1969; 1972 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- New Baltimore, 1950; 1971 (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
- New Lebanon, 1950; 1957; 1980 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- New York City, Hagstrom's Map of High Spots, Undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
- New York City, Potholes, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- New York City, The Sun Newspaper, ca. 1879 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- New York State, Alcoholism, Rehabilitation, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- New York State, Amusement Parks, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- New York State, Appalachian Trail, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- New York State, Arts, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- New York State, Beekeeping, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- New York State, Bankruptcy, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- New York State, Buildings, Historic, 1911-1973 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- New York State, Buildings, Historic, Preservation, 1962; 1966; 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- New York State, Business, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- New York State, Child Abuse, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- New York State, Churches, Reformed, 1960; Undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
- New York State, Community Planning, 1953; 1957 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- New York State, Digest on Laws Affecting Local Government, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- New York State, Drainage Basin Committees' Reports for the North Atlantic Basins, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- New York State, Drugs and Youth, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- New York State, Drugs, Enforcement, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- New York State, Economic Action Bond Act, 1972-1982 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- New York State, Fairs, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- New York State, Festivals, Music, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- New York State, Finances, Public, 1974; 1977-1978; 1981 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- New York State, Fishing, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
- New York State Flag, History, Undated (Box 11, Folder 83)
- New York State, Gambling, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 84)
- New York State, Geology, 1955; 1982 (Box 11, Folder 85)
- New York State, Government and Politics, 1936-1937; 1963; 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- New York State, Government and Politics, 1938 (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
- New York State, Historical Markers, 1958; 1972 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- New York State, Hudson Fulton Celebration, 1909 (Oversized 4, Folder 5)
- New York State, Illiteracy, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 88)
- New York State, Insurance, Car, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- New York State, Insurance, Life, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- New York State, Insurance, Malpractice, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 91)
- New York State, Jaycees, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 92)
- New York State, Job Programs and Training, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 93)
- New York State, Judges, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- New York State, Landfills, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 95)
- New York State, Lead Contamination, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 96)
- New York State, Police, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 97)
- New York State, Police, State, 1966; 1973; 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 11, Folder 98)
- New York State, Pollution, Air, 1971; 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 99)
- New York State, Pollution, Water, 1965; 1970-1971; 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 11, Folder 100)
- New York State, Postal Service, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 101)
- New York State, Postcards, 1907-1965; Undated (Box 11, Folder 102)
- New York State, Prisons, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 103)
- New York State, Schools, Public, 1963; 1966; 1979 (Box 11, Folder 104)
- New York State, Seventh Regiment National Guard, 1868 (Box 11, Folder 105)
- New York State, Spousal Abuse, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 106)
- New York State, Vietnam War, 1966; 1972 (Box 11, Folder 107)
- New York State, Welfare, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 108)
- New York State, Year of History, ca. 1959 (Box 11, Folder 109)
- New Yorker's Idea of the USA, ca. 1937 (Box 11, Folder 110)
- Newburgh, Singer Manufacturing, New York State Pocket Map, Undated (Box 11, Folder 111)
- Newburgh, Singer Manufacturing, New York State Pocket Map, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
- Newtonville, 1963; 1966 (Box 11, Folder 112)
- Niagara Falls, 1903; 1914; 1922; 1924; Undated (Box 11, Folder 113)
- Niskayuna, 1964-1965; 1973; 1978; 1980; Undated (Box 11, Folder 114)
- Niskayuna, O.D. Development Center, 1977; 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 115)
- North Creek, Bigotry, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 116)
- North Hudson, Frontier Town, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 117)
- North Hudson, Roth's Forge, 1967 (Oversized 1, Folder 19)
- Old Chatham, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 118)
- Old Chatham, Shaker Museum, 1956-1980; Undated (Box 11, Folder 119)
- Old Chatham, Shaker Museum, 1958-1959; 1962-1963; 1965; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 6)
- Poestenkill, 1959; 1972 (Box 11, Folder 120)
- Ravena-Coeymans, 1950 (Oversized 4, Folder 7)
- Ravena-Coeymans, 1956-1957; 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 121)
- Rensselaer, 1949-1980; Undated (Box 11, Folder 122)
- Rensselaer, Forbes Manor, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 123)
- Rensselaer, Business and Industry, 1955-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 124)
- Rensselaer County, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 11, Folder 125)
- Rensselaer County, Anniversary Celebration, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 126)
- Rensselaer County, Boundaries, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 127)
- Rensselaer County Council of the Arts, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 128)
- Rensselaer County, Government and Politics, 1972; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 11, Folder 129)
- Rensselaer County Jail, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Rensselaer County, Little Hoosick River, 1954 (Oversized 4, Folder 8)
- Rensselaer County, News, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Rensselaer County, Sterling Winthrop, 1956-1958 (Oversized 4, Folder 9)
- Rensselaer County, Sterling Winthrop, 1959; 1962-1963; 1966; 1978-1979; 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Rensselaer, Fort Crailo, 1916-1980; Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Rensselaer, Fort Crailo, 1936 (Oversized 4, Folder 10)
- Rensselaer, Government and Politics, 1973-1974; 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Rensselaer, History, 1952 (Oversized 4, Folder 11)
- Rensselaer, Housing, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Rensselaer, Schools, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Rensselaerville, 1945-1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Rensselaerville, Institute of Man and Science, 1965-1966; 1968-1969; 1971-1973; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Rochester, Powers Building, Stereoscopic Photograph, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Round Lake, 1968; 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Round Top, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Salem, Revolutionary Soldiers, 1954 (Oversized 4, Folder 12)
- Sand Lake, 1967; 1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Saratoga County, Brochures, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Saratoga County, Government and Politics, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Saratoga County, History and Historic Places, 1972-1973; 1975; 1978; 1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Saratoga National Historic Park, 1962; 1967; 1974; 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Saratoga Springs, American Ballet School, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Saratoga Springs, Baths and Spas, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Saratoga Springs Department of Public Works, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Saratoga Springs, Description and Travel, 1976-1979; 1981; 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Saratoga Springs, Horse Racing, 1918; 1977-1979; 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Saratoga Springs, Mineral Water, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Saratoga Springs Performing Arts Center, 1970; 1972-1974; 1977-1981; Undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Saratoga Springs, Skidmore College, 1963-1981; Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Saratoga Springs, Yaddo, 1977; 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Saugerties, Environmentalism, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Scenic Hudson News, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Schaefer, Vincent, 1989-1990; 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Schaghticoke, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Schaghticoke, Knickerbocker Mansion, 1957; 1960; 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Schenectady, 109th Tactical Airlift Group, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Schenectady, City Plan, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Schenectady, Community Development, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Schenectady County Airport, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Schenectady County, Brochures, 1972; Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Schenectady County Community College, 1964; 1969; 1977-1981; 1985; Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Schenectady County Community College, 1969 (Oversized 1, Folder 20)
- Schenectady County, Government and Politics, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Schenectady County, History, 1954-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Schenectady County, History, 1957; 1959; 1961 (Oversized 4, Folder 13)
- Schenectady County, Hoffman's Ferry Fault, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Schenectady County, Industry, 1956-1981 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Schenectady County, Industry, 1956; 1960 (Oversized 4, Folder 14)
- Schenectady County Jail, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Schenectady County, Maps, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Schenectady County, Medical Facilities, 1960-1962; 1966; 1973; 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Schenectady County, Schools, Public, 1972-1973; 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Schenectady, Government and Politics, 1973; 1975; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Schenectady High School, Class of 1922, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Schenectady, Historic Stockade, 1959-1978; Undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Schenectady, Housing, 1966; 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Schenectady Museum, 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Schenectady, Police, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Schenectady, Postcards, 1915 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Schenectady, Proctor's Theater, 1968; 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Schenectady Report and Manual, ca. 1952; ca. 1954; ca. 1955 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Schenectady, Tornado, 1960 (Oversized 4, Folder 15)
- Schenectady, Union College (1 of 2), 1960-1966; 1972-1973; 1977-1980; Undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Schenectady, Union College (2 of 2), 1960-1966; 1972-1973; 1977-1980; Undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Schenectady Union Star, 1957 (Oversized 4, Folder 16)
- Schenectady, Urban Renewal, 1966; 1969; 1971-1973; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Schodack, 1950 (Oversized 4, Folder 17)
- Schodack, 1966; 1978 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Schuylerville, 1952; 1955; 1957 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Schuylerville, 1957 (Oversized 4, Folder 19)
- Schoharie County, 1949 (Oversized 4, Folder 18)
- Schoharie County, 1959-1978; Undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Scotia, 1959; 1966; 1979 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Selkirk, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Selkirk and Becker's Corners, 1950 (Oversized 4, Folder 20)
- Sharon Springs, 1954 (Oversized 4, Folder 21)
- Sharon Springs, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Slingerlands, 1961-1963; 1966; 1972; Undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Slingerlands, Colonial Style Home, 1962 (Oversized 4, Folder 22)
- Stillwater, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Stockport, 1950 (Oversized 4, Folder 23)
- Syracuse, Empire State Games, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Tekakwitha, Kateri, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Thousand Islands, 1905; Undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Ticonderoga, Fort, 1921; 1951; 1969 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Troy, Bridge Bash, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Troy, Buildings and Places, Historic, 1959-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Troy, Business and Industry, 1969; 1972-1973; 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Troy, Community Development, 1973; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Troy, Description, 1974; 1978; 1980; Undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Troy, Emma Willard School, 1958 (Oversized 4, Folder 24)
- Troy, Emma Willard School, 1960-1961; 1966; 1978 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- Troy, Government and Politics, 1972-1973; 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- Troy, History, 1937-1979 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Troy, Hope Seven Community Center, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- Troy, Housing, 1963; 1966; 1973; 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- Troy, Hudson Mohawk Industrial Gateway, 1972; 1974; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
- Troy, Hudson River Celebration, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 81)
- Troy, Hudson Valley Community College, 1960-1961; 1969-1970; 1977-1980; Undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Troy, Hudson Valley Community College, 1960-1961 (Oversized 4, Folder 25)
- Troy, Kennedy Korps, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Troy, Music Hall, 1959 (Oversized 1, Folder 21)
- Troy, Music Hall, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 84)
- Troy, Police, 1973; 1978 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- Troy, Rensselaer County Historical Society, 1971; 1978; Undated (Box 12, Folder 86)
- Troy, Rensselaer County Junior Museum, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
- Troy, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1956 (Oversized 4, Folder 26)
- Troy, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1960-1981; Undated (Box 12, Folder 88)
- Troy, Schools, Public, 1973; 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 89)
- Troy, Uncle Sam, 1958-1980; Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Troy, Uncle Sam, 1959 (Oversized 1, Folder 22)
- Ulster County, Brochures and Guides, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- U.S.S. Albany, 1959; 1962-1963; 1968; 1979-1980; Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Voorheesville, 1956 (Oversized 4, Folder 27)
- Voorheesville, 1963; Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Waterford, 1952; 1963; 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Waterford, Industry, 1956 (Oversized 4, Folder 28)
- Waterford, Industry, 1962; 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Watervliet, 1957; 1973; 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Watervliet, Industry, 1952-1980; Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Watervliet, Industry, 1956; 1960; 1966 (Oversized 4, Folder 29)
- Watkins Glen, Stereoscopic Photograph, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)